{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Elevator \u0026 Lift Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40279/":{"taskOID":40279,"originalTaskOID":40279,"setID":582,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4517,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Lift","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of elevator or chair lift needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200964,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stairway lift","answerDisplayText":"Stairway lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6681,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vertical platform or wheelchair lift","answerDisplayText":"Vertical platform or wheelchair lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4812,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Portable wheelchair lift","answerDisplayText":"Portable wheelchair lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2114,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dumbwaiter","answerDisplayText":"Dumbwaiter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3040,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home elevator with enclosed cab","answerDisplayText":"Home elevator with enclosed cab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202091,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Commercial elevator","answerDisplayText":"Commercial elevator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4516,"questionDisplayText":"Describe Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3973,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Motor runs but elevator/lift doesn't move","answerDisplayText":"Motor runs but elevator/lift doesn't move","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3573,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lift stuck in position mid floor","answerDisplayText":"Lift stuck in position mid floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3572,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lift stuck in position at floor level","answerDisplayText":"Lift stuck in position at floor level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3571,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lift is unstable","answerDisplayText":"Lift is unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1243,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Car gate is not functioning properly","answerDisplayText":"Car gate is not functioning properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3724,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Makes odd noise while in operation","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noise while in operation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5458,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Safety mechanisms need repair or adjustments","answerDisplayText":"Safety mechanisms need repair or adjustments","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4100,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Needs general servicing","answerDisplayText":"Needs general servicing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4509,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Lift","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the location of the lift?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4472,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoor covered","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor covered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":70000,"questionDisplayText":"Financing Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need financing?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4517,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Lift","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of elevator or chair lift needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200964,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stairway lift","answerDisplayText":"Stairway lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6681,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vertical platform or wheelchair lift","answerDisplayText":"Vertical platform or wheelchair lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4812,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Portable wheelchair lift","answerDisplayText":"Portable wheelchair lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2114,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dumbwaiter","answerDisplayText":"Dumbwaiter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3040,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home elevator with enclosed cab","answerDisplayText":"Home elevator with enclosed cab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202091,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Commercial elevator","answerDisplayText":"Commercial elevator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200964,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stairway lift","answerDisplayText":"Stairway lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6681,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Vertical platform or wheelchair lift","answerDisplayText":"Vertical platform or wheelchair lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4812,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Portable wheelchair lift","answerDisplayText":"Portable wheelchair lift","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2114,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dumbwaiter","answerDisplayText":"Dumbwaiter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3040,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home elevator with enclosed cab","answerDisplayText":"Home elevator with enclosed cab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202091,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Commercial elevator","answerDisplayText":"Commercial elevator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4516,"questionDisplayText":"Describe Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3973,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Motor runs but elevator/lift doesn't move","answerDisplayText":"Motor runs but elevator/lift doesn't move","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3573,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lift stuck in position mid floor","answerDisplayText":"Lift stuck in position mid floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3572,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lift stuck in position at floor level","answerDisplayText":"Lift stuck in position at floor level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3571,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lift is unstable","answerDisplayText":"Lift is unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1243,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Car gate is not functioning properly","answerDisplayText":"Car gate is not functioning properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3724,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Makes odd noise while in operation","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noise while in operation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5458,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Safety mechanisms need repair or adjustments","answerDisplayText":"Safety mechanisms need repair or adjustments","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4100,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Needs general servicing","answerDisplayText":"Needs general servicing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3973,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Motor runs but elevator/lift doesn't move","answerDisplayText":"Motor runs but elevator/lift doesn't move","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3573,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lift stuck in position mid floor","answerDisplayText":"Lift stuck in position mid floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3572,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lift stuck in position at floor level","answerDisplayText":"Lift stuck in position at floor level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3571,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Lift is unstable","answerDisplayText":"Lift is unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1243,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Car gate is not functioning properly","answerDisplayText":"Car gate is not functioning properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3724,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Makes odd noise while in operation","answerDisplayText":"Makes odd noise while in operation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5458,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Safety mechanisms need repair or adjustments","answerDisplayText":"Safety mechanisms need repair or adjustments","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4100,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Needs general servicing","answerDisplayText":"Needs general servicing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4509,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Lift","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the location of the lift?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4472,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoor covered","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor covered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4472,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoor covered","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor covered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":70000,"questionDisplayText":"Financing Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need financing?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40279/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40279,"taskName":"Elevator or Stairlift - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair an Elevator or Stairlift","xmTaskDescriptor":"Elevator \u0026 Lift Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1716,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Disability Elevator Chair elevators list Stairlift","textMessagingName":"Repr Disabil Elev","rolloverLongDesc":"Diagnose \u0026 solve problems with an elevator or chair lift that is already in place. Typically used in larger, luxurious homes or when personal mobility is limited.","rolloverShortDesc":"Correct a problem with an existing elevator or stairlift.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair an Elevator or Stairlift.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Elevator Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Stairlift Repair | Fix Wheelchair Lift","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":28,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Elevator or Stairlift Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Elevator or Stairlift - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Elevator or Stairlift Project","urlName":"Elevator-or-Chairlift-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Elevator Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs, Reviews","searchKeywords":"Disability,Elevator,Chair,elevators,list,Stairlift,Lift","emcCategoryOid":-12021,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":582,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}